parentingnation.in 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policies of Parenting Portal Parenting Nation India - Parenting Nation India

**Introduction:**

Hello and welcome to Parenting Nation. We designed this privacy policy to share with you our method of collecting and using any information or data provided by users through our site. we request you to make sure complete reading and understanding of our privacy policy before utilizing and sending any information to our site.

**User Approval:**

Once users utilize this site, user accept all terms of our privacy policy. The information users provide to our site, agree to collect, use and disclose that information or data as per this privacy policy.

**For Parents:**

Our site is developed and is intended to create baby photo contest just for fun. Any personal information provided by age group under 13 can be used unknowingly. we want our members, users and visitors to provide any information or data regarding kids or children after the consent of their parents. We ask parents to talk to their kids about the use of any personal information on internet.

**Your Content in our Services  **

For content that is covered by intellectual property rights, like photos and videos (IP content), you specifically give us the following permission, subject to your privacy and application settings: you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any IP content that you post on or in connection with our products (IP License). This IP License ends when you delete your IP content or your account unless your content has been shared with others, and they have not deleted it.

When you delete IP content, it is deleted in a manner similar to emptying the recycle bin on a computer. However, you understand that removed content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others). 

When you use an application, your content and information is shared with the application. We require applications to respect your privacy, and your agreement with that application will control how the application can use, store, and transfer that content and information.

When you publish content or information using the Public setting, it means that you are allowing everyone, including people outside of our services, to access and use that information, and to associate it with you (i.e. your name and profile picture).

We always appreciate your feedback or other suggestions about our Services, but you understand that we may use them without any obligation to compensate you for them (just as you have no obligation to offer them).

We are not liable for loss of any data caused by unforeseen circumstances.

Should you wish to move your data from our site, we are not liable to provide this data to you in any format.

**This site is for India so gift can be sent to addresses of India only.**

**Use of Parentination Articles & Information **

Different kind of Content, Advices, Articles, Comments, text, Post, Photographs and other data is available on the Parenting nation. This all content is provided by Writers hired by parentination and people who is visiting our site. Parenting nation is not responsible for any inaccurate or unauthenticated content. Any advice or opinion made by any kind of user on the website is not endorsed by parenting nation and we don’t take any responsibility for the same. This all Content is provided in consideration that neither parentingnation nor it suppliers are part of any Medical, Legal or any kind of Counseling. And all content is to be used as just general informative content and not to be used for any Medical or Health Related problems. We would suggest for any Medical or Health Related problems please consult your physician or qualified doctor.

**Information or Data From User:**

Information collected from the site can be used in following ways.

To make our site better by improving functions on feedback we receive.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To Run a photo contest, Take surveys and other promotion activity.

**Newsletter emails :**

You may receive some newsletters from us regarding contest and other service, we have provided unsubscribe link so if you dont want any further emails pls unsubscribe from the site. .

Our site gathers information from our members by asking questions and we also get in touch by communicating through e-mail, Face book, Twitter, and parents forum. the communication may include some personal information also, like name, e-mail id, phone number, detail address, photos and may be more. Our site also demand some personal information from users to let them have maximum benefits of our features like, vaccination chart, parenting information, advise/suggestions, gifts and so on. the information demanded can be for participating on some area of our site like baby photo contest. Users will be guided at every step of information demanded.

**Upload, Change and Remove:**

With an intention to keep the personal information provided is accurate, users may contact us as below and we will make sure of necessary steps to make upload, change or remove personalize data or information, if our site has no further use of the data or information we may destroy the information or data.

**Contact Us:**

To upload, change and remove your personal details on our site e-mail us on [info@parentingnation.in](mailto:info@parentingnation.in).
